(Nathan Fillion:)Oh, yeah, I get it--
you think I'm Nathan Fillion,
(Nathan Fillion:)but I'm not.
(Nathan Fillion:)So if you don't mind, I would
just love to eat my lunch.
(Raj:)Come on.
(Leonard:)Sorry to bother you.
(Raj:)Don't know why
he's so grumpy.
(Raj:)I got mistaken for that guy
in Life of Pi once,
(Raj:)and I'm still
floating.
(Amy:)Sheldon, it's me.
(Penny:)Oh, hey.
D-Did you see that?
I-I figured out how to open
the door all by myself.
Maybe I'll fling some feces
around my cage to celebrate.
(Amy:)What are you talking about?
(Penny:)I know you've been giving me
secret puzzle tests.
(Amy:)Sheldon, open
the door.
SHELDON:
I can't.
(Sheldon:)I'm naked.
(Amy:)I just saw you.
(Sheldon:)Hang on.
(Penny:)Open the door now.
(door opens)
Oh, hey.
Pull up your pants!